Shrey Bhadiyadara

Full Stack Developer

shreybhadiyadara33@gmail.com • +917874527250

https://www.linkedin.com/in/shrey-bhadiyadara-5ab45b190/ • https://github.com/shrey333 • https://shreyb.vercel.app/

Summary

Full stack developer with expertise in the user interface, testing, and debugging procedures. Having experience in web system design, implementation, testing, and maintenance.

Skills

React • Angular • Flutter • Spring boot • Django • PHP • Node.js • .net core

Work Experience

Full Stack Developer

Jan 2022 - Jun 2022 • 5 mos

Suvit Fintech Pvt. Ltd. • Full-time

Surat, India

Technologies: React • Socket.io • Node.js • Redux • MongoDB

- Suvit helps customers by reducing their effort and time in the process of manual entry in any accounting software (eg. Tally)
- · Worked upon migration of TallyWiz(former brand) to Suvit
- · Made application real-time with help of socket.io
- Managed to alleviate performance issues in the application
- Reduced average loading time from above 2 seconds to below 0.8 seconds

Project Intern Dec 2021 – Apr 2022 • 4 mos

LG CSR's Shabdamitra project • Internship

Remote

Technologies: Flutter • Sqlite • Material design

- Shabdamitra is a learning aid project developed by IIT-Bombay and LG India(CSR team)
- Developed easy to use and offline android application
- Worked on migration of MySQL to SQLite database
- · Worked specifically on making UI intuitive and user friendly

Projects

UniCollab Jan 2021 - Apr 2021 • 3 mos

2 coworkers

Technologies: Flutter • Firebase • Firestore

UniCollab is made for ease of sharing educational resources(like classroom material, upcoming announcements, and assignments) between teachers and students.

<u>Online Book Service</u> Jan 2021 - Apr 2021 • 3 mos

Technologies: Spring boot • Jsp • Sqlite • pdf.js

Online Book Service allows users to either buy or read or publish books online. It also allows users to search for books. It uses custom Pdfjs renderer to render pdfs.

Discussion Forum Jan 2021 - Apr 2021 • 3 mos

1 coworker

Technologies: .net core • Sql server • Bootstrap

Discussion Forum provides an interface to discuss any random topic with users of the platform. Users can reply to other users' comments.

The Queue Platform

Jul 2020 - Oct 2020 • 3 mos

Technologies: Angular • Node.js • Express JS • MongoDB

The queue platform is a place where people can join the queue of nearby stores for a fee and merchants or store owners can register their shops on the platform. This platform provides people with social distance during these pandemics.

<u>TechFest</u> Jan 2020 - Apr 2020 • 3 mos

Technologies: Python • Django • MySQL

TechFest is a platform where universities can organize their technical festival and students from various universities can participate in the events.

Educations

Bachelor's degree: Computer Engineering

Jul 2018 - Apr 2022 • 3 yrs 9 mos

Dharmsinh Desai University

India

Grade/GPA: 8.9/10.00

Courses in algorithms, data structures, artificial intelligence, machine learning, programming languages, computer architecture, operating systems, databases, theory of computation, compiler design, and many others cover important components of theory, abstraction, and design.